Make some more noise, man. Make some
more noise. Come
>> [cheering]
>> We in here.
Everybody in here, Anaheim, okay?
White people, make some noise. All
right.
All right.
Black people, make some noise.
>> [cheering]
>> Okay? Okay. I thought it was don't tell
us at first. I thought that's who they
didn't tell.
Who did they forget to tell? No, it's
good. Shout out my Hispanic people. I
don't like what's going on with the ICE
situation at the airports and all that
[\h__\h] Shout out all my Mexican people.
That's [\h__\h] up. I be trying to help my
Mexican people.
I'm doing the underground railroad
program. I live in Atlanta.
I take them to black barber shops and
and get them fades and give them durags.
Give them some wave grease. I say, "See
if you can get some waves. You not Juan,
you the one. Okay?" If they call you
Juan, don't look.
>> [cheering]
>> No, man. [screaming] Hey, man. I rock
with the Mexican people, man.
What would LA be without Mexicans?
Nobody want no beef Wellington from a
food truck. What is that?
>> [laughter]
>> They selling quiche? It's 2:00 in the
morning. Nobody want that.
>> [laughter]
>> No, it's look. All right. Listen. All
right.
I'm just saying, white people is See,
y'all y'all lost the plot, man.
Somewhere along the way, y'all lost
Y'all forgot who you were.
Y'all used to be cool in your own way.
Now you just take black people phrases
and [\h__\h] them up for everybody.
Y'all used to have your own lingo, your
own slang. Now y'all just take our [\h__\h]
Woke is done. Y'all done burnt woke the
[\h__\h] out.
Woke don't even mean what it meant. For
black people, it meant stay alert, pay
attention to what's going on.
Y'all done turned it into meaning
superheroes not supposed to have titties
if they didn't have titties in the
comic. [laughter] What the [\h__\h] ARE YOU
TALKING ABOUT?
IS THAT WHAT IT MEANS?
THEY TOOK [\h__\h] AROUND AND FIND OUT.
THE military He didn't even say it
right.
And for those out there
who want to try
FAFO. [\h__\h] FAFO. That's not how it
works.
If you take the [\h__\h] out, it's lost all
its power.
What happened to y'all's phrases, man?
Y'all That's when the economy was the
best when when white dudes had slick
[\h__\h] to say all the time.
You would work and they know how to do
something you don't know how to do and
you Oh, do it like that.
>> [clears throat]
>> You think?
>> [laughter]
>> What are you, SOME KIND OF [\h__\h]
DILLWEED? Remember when y'all used to
Remember?
YOU FORGOT WHO YOU ARE.
UH, no [\h__\h] Sherlock. Remember that?
Remember?
>> [laughter]
>> Remember? This y'all Lion King moment.
Remember who you are.
Shut up.
Go back to y'all's phrases.
Black people just make [\h__\h] sound
better. It just sound cooler. We'll say
some [\h__\h] wrong and it'll still sound
better.
>> [laughter]
>> Black people Sometimes it's not even
a change of words. It just have we say
it. If black people say some [\h__\h] twice,
that means is that much more serious.
>> [laughter]
>> Like if they be like, "Hey, don't go
down to the south side for real for
real."
>> [laughter]
>> That other for real means death. Don't
go down there.
If we doubling up, we not doing it.
>> [laughter]
>> No black person is going out if it's
raining raining. What are you talking
about? It's raining raining.
>> [laughter]
>> I thought it was just raining. No, it's
raining raining.
>> [laughter]
>> Snowing snowing? That's a blizzard. What
are you talking about? No, nobody can go
anywhere if it's snowing snowing.
>> [laughter]
>> This what the [\h__\h] we do, man.
Y'all, we just make [\h__\h] sound better we
leaving. We got so many different ways
to say it.
Just cool, man.
About to slide.
About to bounce.
Man, I guess I'm about to hit it.
I'm out this [\h__\h]
White people, go back to y'all [\h__\h]
Y'all don't sound cool using our [\h__\h]
Go back.
White dudes be getting ready to leave. I
guess it's time to skirt skirt. Stop
doing that.
Yeah, man.
>> [laughter]
[laughter]
>> Stop doing that. Go back to what y'all
used to do.
>> [laughter]
>> Skedaddle. I don't know.
Put the pedal to the metal. Go,
dude. Do what you used to do.
>> [laughter]
>> I'm tired of this [\h__\h] man.
Now, we got to kick it. I like it.
I don't know. Back out here in LA, this
[\h__\h] I lived out here for a little bit.
It made me a worse person, just
It did. It did. It did. I used to help
homeless people. Then I moved out here.
>> [laughter]
>> And I was like, [\h__\h] that. He got more
square feet than I do.
He don't pay nothing.
>> [laughter]
>> This is the only place I seen where
homeless people get to build their
little structure. He got a whole
balcony. I'm like, damn.
>> [laughter]
>> This where you see homeless people with
dogs. I don't think that's right.
Can't have no dog. Not on a leash.
You got to let him choose.
>> [laughter]
>> You know the homeless people with the
dog that's not on a leash, the dog just
right there, that's his dog.
If they got him on a leash, no. Take him
off the leash.
>> [laughter]
>> If he stays here, that's your dog.
>> If he runs off, we know you took him and
you didn't been dragging him along with
your bad decisions. Stop it.
>> [laughter]
>> Let him have a opportunity to be who he
want to be.
Cuz the homeless person look dirty, the
dog look clean. I'm like, that dog could
get a job. That's a
That's a purebred German Shepherd. You
need to take him to the airport, let him
work a few hours.
>> [laughter]
>> Bring you home a treat every night.
And you going to have him on a leash?
That dog don't know he homeless.
He think he on the longest walk ever.
>> [laughter]
>> He think every corner going to be the
house. Just
>> [laughter]
>> You're never going to make it. HE KEEPS
TAKING NAPS.
>> [laughter]
>> ALL RIGHT.
ABOUT TO GET OUT OF HERE.
>> [laughter]
>> Y'ALL TOGETHER?
Y'all dating? Or y'all dating dating?
Y'all married together? Huh? You
engaged? Oh, so y'all [\h__\h] [\h__\h]
OKAY.
YEAH. Raw dog. No, I'm just playing. I'm
just
>> [laughter]
>> No.
Let her win. Let her win all the
arguments. You can't You can't beat your
girl at arguing.
You can't.
You can't. My girl doesn't even use
words the way they meant to be used.
>> [laughter]
>> I asked her, "Hey, did you forget what I
said about taking our son to the park?"
I didn't forget. I just remembered right
now. I was [laughter] like,
This [\h__\h] confused me. I was like, what?
I had to Google what is remember.
Is misremembering a thing?
>> [laughter]
>> You ever gotten an apology from your
girl? That's the worst [\h__\h] in the
world.
>> [laughter]
>> Your girl apologize and you get madder.
>> Because they never apologize for what
they did.
>> [laughter]
>> Their apology is [\h__\h] up.
And they know it's [\h__\h] up.
They deliver it [\h__\h] up. You can tell
by their posture, how they move their
head, everything. [laughter]
I'm sorry if what I said made you
[laughter] feel like I wasn't paying
attention. I didn't realize you were a
[\h__\h] You like, "Hey,
ma'am, turn your head back right.
First of all,
>> [laughter]
>> all right.
No, I like it.
>> [laughter]
>> And women, y'all stop If you got a man
that loves you, just go with what he
says. Believe him. If he's showing you
that, believe him. Don't make him jump
through no extra hoops. Just believe him
if he's showing you that. Okay? Stop
doing that stuff. That's all he wanted
some [\h__\h] That's all you care about is
some [\h__\h]
That's all men want is some [\h__\h]
That's crazy.
Nobody just wants some [\h__\h]
>> [laughter]
>> We want everything that come with the
[\h__\h]
>> [laughter]
>> We like your face, your lips, your body,
everything that come with the [\h__\h]
Have you ever seen just A [\h__\h]
>> [laughter]
>> EW.
EW.
WHAT KIND OF SEA CREATURE is this? A
[\h__\h] Off-the-bone [\h__\h] is wild. That
is crazy. That scares anyone. If you
went home tonight and you went in your
kitchen and it was just a [\h__\h] sitting
on the kitchen counter. EVERYBODY IN
HERE
YOU WOULD CALL ANIMAL CONTROL. I DON'T
KNOW HOW IT GOT IN. I don't know.
>> [laughter]
>> Nobody want just the [\h__\h]
Ew.
That's disgusting.
>> [laughter]
>> But that's not how y'all feel about us.
Ladies, y'all don't care about us.
Y'all just want the dick.
>> [laughter]
>> Separate us from the dick every chance
you get.
Birthday parties, bachelor parties. You
can't get head at the house, but she
drinking out of dick straws.
>> [laughter]
>> She just hired a lady to play the dick
flute when you come in. What kind of
[\h__\h] is this?
They eating dick cake. Ew.
>> [laughter]
>> We don't do no [\h__\h] like that.
It's your homeboy birthday party.
Everybody hide and when he come out they
pop out blowing on CLIP WHISTLES.
YEAH.
>> [laughter]
>> GET YOU SOME OF THE [\h__\h] PIE. SCRAPE
THE hair off. You don't want no hair on
here.
Get a little coochie cupcake. Stick your
finger in there. Mm, that's good.
>> [laughter]
>> Take him to the back so he can beat up
the [\h__\h] pinata. Ew.
Nobody does that, man. Look, hey man,
y'all been amazing. I've been Clayton
English.
Go to jail. Thank y'all.
>> [music]